<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<component>
  <id>org.kde.plasmashell</id>
  <project_license>GPL-2.0+</project_license>
  <name>KDE Plasma Desktop</name>
  <name xml:lang="es">Escritorio KDE Plasma</name>
  <name xml:lang="nl">KDE Plasma Bureaublad</name>
  <name xml:lang="pt">Área de Trabalho Plasma do KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="sv">KDE Plasma skrivbord</name>
  <name xml:lang="uk">Стільниця Плазми KDE</name>
  <name xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE Plasma Desktopxx</name>
  <summary>KDE's complete desktop experience. Simple by default, powerful when needed.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="es">Experiencia completa de escritorio de KDE. Sencillo por omisión, potente cuando es necesario.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="nl">De complete bureaubladvaring van KDE. Standaard eenvoudig, krachtig indien nodig.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="pt">A experiência completa de trabalho do KDE. Simples por omissão, poderosa quando necessário.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="sv">KDE:s fullständiga skrivbordsupplevelse. Normalt enkel, kraftfull vid behov.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="uk">Повноцінне стільничне середовище KDE. Типово просте, але потужне, якщо це потрібно.</summary>
  <summary xml:lang="x-test">xxKDE's complete desktop experience. Simple by default, powerful when needed.xx</summary>
  <url type="homepage">https://www.kde.org/workspaces/plasmadesktop/</url>
  <url type="bugtracker">https://bugs.kde.org/enter_bug.cgi?format=guided&amp;product=plasmashell</url>
  <project_group>KDE</project_group>
  <provides>
    <binary>plasmashell</binary>
  </provides>
  <screenshots>
    <screenshot type="default">
      <caption>Plasma Desktop in Folder View with Clock and Notes Widgets</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="es">Escritorio Plasma en modo de vista de carpeta con reloj y notas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="nl">Plasma-bureaublad in mapweergave met klok en notitie-widgets</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="pt">Ecrã do Plasma na Área de Pastas com o Relógio e as Notas</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="sv">Plasma skrivbord i katalogvy med de grafiska komponenterna Klocka och Anteckningar</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="uk">Стільниця Плазми на панелі перегляду тек із віджетами годинника і нотаток</caption>
      <caption xml:lang="x-test">xxPlasma Desktop in Folder View with Clock and Notes Widgetsxx</caption>
      <image type="source">https://www.kde.org/workspaces/plasmadesktop/screenshots/general-desktop.png</image>
    </screenshot>
  </screenshots>
</component>
